bookfunnel.com 2019-02-17

# Privacy Policy : BookFunnel

_Last updated: April 24, 2018_

### Who we are

Our website address is https://bookfunnel.com.

BOOKFUNNEL LLC is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes how we collect, use, and disclose data. This Policy applies to your use of BookFunnel’s services and Website located at <https://bookfunnel.com/> (“Services”).

BookFunnel is a United States limited liability company subject to the laws of the United States. The United States may not offer a level of privacy protection equal to that offered in other jurisdictions. Our servers are located in the United States, and your data may be transferred to, stored, or processed in the United States. By using our service, you understand and consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your data to our facilities in the United States and those third parties we share your data with as described in this Policy and our Terms of Service Agreement.

### What data we collect

BookFunnel may collect two kinds of information about you: (a) Personal Data; and (b) Non-Personal Data.

**Personal Data**. Personal Data we may collect includes name, email address, and IP address. You may decline to provide Personal Data to BookFunnel. However, some of the Personal Data we ask you to provide is mandatory for a service. If you decline to provide it, we may not be able to provide that service to you.

**Non-Personal Data**. Non-Personal Data is any information not relating to an identifiable person. Non-Personal Data we may collect includes device type, device manufacturer and model, type of browser or operating system, dates and times of use, and screen resolution. We may also track the book pages you visit while on the site.

### How we use your data

**Personal Data**. We may use your Personal Data to provide the Services; verify your identity and the information you provide; customize your experience; and provide customer service via email if requested.

**Non-Personal Data**. We may use your Non-Personal Data for any purpose, including, but not limited to, providing customer service via email if requested.

### Where we send your data

We will never sell, rent, or lease your Personal Data to a third party.

**Personal Data**. We may disclose, and you consent to our disclosing of, your Personal Data to:

  1. Service Providers who help with our business operations and assist in the delivery of our Services including, but not limited to, email delivery services, payment processing, and enforcement of our Terms of Service Agreement and other agreements;
  2. Persons or entities with whom you consent to have your Personal Data shared (Example: the author of the book you downloaded);
  3. Third parties as we believe necessary or appropriate, in any manner permitted under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence to: comply with legal process; respond to requests from public and government authorities, including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; enforce our Terms of Service Agreement and other agreements; protect our operations; protect our rights, privacy, safety or property; and allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

**Non-Personal Data**. We may disclose Non-Personal Data for any purpose. Remember, Non-Personal Data cannot be used to identify you or another person.

### Advertising

BookFunnel does not use your personal data for any advertising purposes.

### How we protect your data

We employ commercially reasonable security measures to protect your information; however, no system is impenetrable. If you create an account on the Services, you are responsible for protecting the security of your account, its content, and all activities that occur under the account. You must immediately notify BookFunnel of any unauthorized uses of your account or any other breaches of security by emailing us at [legal@bookfunnel.com](mailto:legal@bookfunnel.com).

### How long we retain your data

We will retain your Personal Data for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or allowed by law.

### What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### Third party websites

The inclusion of a link or accessibility of third-party sites does not imply endorsement of such third-party site by us. Any trademarks, trade names, and logos of third parties featured belong to their respective owners. Each third-party processor collects and shares your information according to its own privacy policy and terms of service. BookFunnel is not responsible for the actions of third-party processors, including how such entities treat your information. You are responsible for knowing and understanding their policies and terms.

### Embedded Content From Other Websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. instructional videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Users under 13 years of age

Our Services are not directed to and we do not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with Personal Data, we will take steps to remove such data. If you become aware that your child has provided us with Personal Data without your consent, please contact us at [legal@bookfunnel.com](mailto:legal@bookfunnel.com). By using BookFunnel.com, you are representing to us that you are not under the age of 13.

### Privacy right notice to California Residents

The State of California enacted the Shine the Light law (California Civil Code Section 1798.83) that permits users who are California residents to request certain information regarding the disclosure of certain “personal information” during the past year for marketing purposes. To make such a request, please email us at[legal@bookfunnel.com](mailto:legal@bookfunnel.com).

### Changes to this privacy policy

BookFunnel may change this Privacy Policy at any time. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy is indicated by the “Last Updated” date at the top of the Privacy Policy. All changes are effective immediately upon posting. Please review this Privacy Policy frequently to stay updated on changes that may affect you. Your continued use of the Services signifies your continuing consent to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

### Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [legal@bookfunnel.com](mailto:legal@bookfunnel.com).

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name and email address in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
